Four days gone, the engine sighs But there's no
mercy in my eyes My body screams it's morning
light And it's cold and endless rush hour nights
My screen is dark, my phone is dead Just static
roaring in my head A stranger in a strange new
town As the evening rain comes pouring down I
hear the lie in your fake surprise Reflected in
the payphone's hollow eyes You never told her we
were on our way You just decided you would stay
and now Now I know I'll never see The home that's
waiting back for me This is the end, my final plea
Lost on this rainy Stewart Street
I hear you talk of traffic jams Of sudden trips
and altered plans Your voice as sweet as sugar
shell Hiding the keys to my new hell The number
150 you say Another bus to take me away Not close
to home but to the cage you've built with your own
bitter rage And I hear the lie in your fake
surprise reflect in the payphones hollow eyes
you never told her we were on our way you just
decided you would stay and now i know i'll never
see the home that's waiting back for me this is
the end my I finally lost time, this rain is too
much strain.
I love
you.
And I hear the lie in your fake surprise
Reflected in the payphone's hollow eyes You
never told her we were on our way You just decided
you would stay And now I know I'll never see The
home that's waiting back For me, this is the end,
my final plea Lost on this rainy Stuart street